Preliminary Inventory to the United States. Fuel Administration Records, 1916-1919
Hoover Institution Archives
United States. Fuel Administration Records,
1916-1919
70036
United States. Fuel Administration
3 manuscript boxes 1.2 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Press releases, minutes of meetings, and printed matter, relating to production, distribution, and conservation of fuel in the U.S. during World War I
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1970.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Fuel--United States.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1914-1918--Economic aspects.; World War, 1914-1918--United States.; United States--Politics and government.
Container List
- Press releases (Box 1.)
  - 1917
    - September 5-October 31
    - November 1-30
    - December 1-31
  - 1918
    - January 1-31
    - March 1-April 30 (Box 2.)
    - May 1-June 29
    - July 1-August 31
    - September 3-October 31
    - November 1-December 31
  - 1919 (Box 3.)
    - January 2-March 29
- Minutes of meetings of the National Coal Association, 1917 June 27-1918 June 20
- Bates, Lindon W., "Colloidal Fuel: Composites of Oil and Carbon," 1918
- United States. Fuel Administration. Publications, no. 1 ff., 1917 August 23, and miscellaneous printed material
- Addresses of members of the U.S. Fuel Administration
- "Joint Conference of Coal Operators and Coal Miners of the Central Competitive Field," western Pennsylvania, Ohio, Indiana and Illinois, 1916